《越狱》第四季 第三集
Prison.Break.S04E03
《越狱》剧情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
我提供给你的是一个免除15年刑期的机会
I'm giving you an opportunity to avoid 15 years in jail.
-用什么交换  -锡拉
In exchange for? Scylla.
这些是脚踝全球定位跟踪器
These are GPS ankle monitors.
我是你们的头
I'm your boss.
我让你们带上跟踪器
And if I ask you to put on a monitor.
你们就带上跟踪器
You put on a monitor.
惠斯勒的任务是把锡拉交给一名公司高管
Whistler assignment was to drop off Scylla to a Company executive.
他的任务是保护锡拉
And his job was to protect it.
当这一切结束以后  你和我
When this is, when this is all done, you and me.
我们要做个了断
We're gonna settle up.
我找阿历克斯
I'm looking for Alex.
-妈妈  -我们没什么好谈的
-Mom! -We're done talking.
你不能进去
You don't want to go in there.
迈克尔・斯科菲尔德和林肯・布鲁斯在哪
Where are Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows?
我发誓  我真的不知道他们在哪
I swear to you, I've no idea where they are.
怎么了
What's wrong?
不管它是什么  反正不对
Whatever it is, it ain't it.
假如说锡拉是块披萨  我们得到的只是一片
If Scylla was like a pizza, all we got's a slice.
这么说锡拉不只是一张卡
So Scylla isn't one card.
是六张
It's six.
-你把我们卷进什么之中了  -什么
-What'd you pull us into? -Excuse me?
你以为你把我们骗过来了
You figured you'd get us on the hook.
我们之后就能发现...
So we could find out for ourselves...
整件事有多他妈的麻烦
How screwed this whole thing was!
你到底在说什么
What the hell exactly are you talking about?
数据卡  赛尔夫特工  我说的是卡
The card, Agent Self! I'm talking about the card!
-根本没有用  -等等  等一下
-It's useless! -Wait, wait, hold on.
你已经得到数据卡了
You already got the card?
是的  但没有其余的5张卡  就毫无意义
Yes, but without the other five cards, it means nothing!
而我认为你早就知道
And I can only assume you knew that!
其他五张什么卡
What other five?
别装了
Don't.
其他五张什么卡
What other five?
罗兰下载了卡里的数据
Roland downloaded the card.
卡里没有公司的资料
There's no Company data on the card.
没有其他五张卡  这张就无法读取
So without the other five cards, it's unreadable.
这就像是谜题的6分之1一样
It's like one-sixth of the puzzle.
但这不是我的问题
But that's not my problem.
-因为我们有协议  我们已经...  -不
-Because we had a deal, and we gave you...  -No.
-把你要的东西拿到了  -不  没有  你们没有
-Exactly what you asked for. -No, you didn't! No, you didn't!
我们的协议是你帮我搞到锡拉
We had a deal for you to get me Scylla.
你们没还没搞到  对吧
And you haven't gotten me that, have you?
你向我保证过的
You gave me your word.
我再向你保证一次  如果你们...
And I'm giving you my word again, you will go...
不能把另外5张卡弄到手  就滚回监狱去
Back to prison if you can't get me those other five cards.
但如果你告诉我  你无法做到的话
But if you're telling me you can't get this done.
现在就告诉我  我们会把牢房帮你们准备好的
Just let me know right now, and we'll get your cell ready.
明白吗
You understand？
我会搞定的
I'll get it done.
还有一件事情
There's one more thing.
他怎么说的
So what'd he say?
我们要找到其余的卡
We got to find the other cards.
滚蛋吧  伙计  我们得到卡了  进行第二步吧
Screw that, man. We got the card, let's do the second step.
闯入那一步  结束这一切
The break-in thing, and end all this.
现在那样做没用了
It doesn't work that way now.
这不公平  我们照他说的做了
It's not fair. We did what he said.
那给赛尔夫特工电话  说你想回福克斯河监狱
Then call Agent Self, tell him you want to go back to Fox River.
该死  如果找不到其余的卡  我们都得进监狱
Hell, we're all going to prison if we cannot find the other cards.
当政府感觉事情不妙之后
When the government the gets scared.
他们会先将自己置身度外
They tend to cut the cord.
赛尔夫提过让我们结束任务吗
Did Self talk about shutting us down?
我们还是集中精力找锡拉吧  好吗
Let's just concentrate on finding Scylla, all right?
阿历克斯.
Alex.
他要去哪
Where's he going?
管他呢
Who cares?
我们都不知从哪入手  怎么找锡拉
How are we gonna find Scylla? We don't even know where to start.
你找到的其他东西在哪
Where's the rest of the stuff you found?
还在打印
Still printing it up.
我的东西之前肯定被放在了...
When my device was in Tuxhorn's house...
塔克豪恩家靠近他掌上电脑的地方
It must've been left next to his PDA.
拷贝了里面所有的数据  邮件和照片
Sucked up all the data from it and got e-mails and photos.
有我们需要的信息吗
You see anything we can use?
没有  我跟你们说清楚  我只负责电脑
No, and let me be crystal clear for you guys: I point and click.
仅此而已  其他的事我一概不管
That's it, other than that, I'm off the clock.
闭嘴
Shut up.
等等  他的日程表在哪
Wait a minute, where's his calendar?
在自我感觉良好的医生那
Dr. Feelgood's got it.
在这儿  看看这个
Here, um, take a look at this.
这是今天的日程
This is today's date.
上面除了一颗星之外  什么都没有
There's absolutely nothing on it but a star.
其他日期塔克豪恩都详细写明了...
Every other date, Tuxhorn has details for his...
会面和会议的参与者  时间和地点的信息
Appointments and meetings, who he's with, when and where.
只有今天的日程什么都没写
This is the only thing with nothing on it.
他这么做一定是有原因的
It must be a reason he's keeping that secret.
我们为何不让赛尔夫那家伙做决定
Why are we letting this Self guy call all the shots?
也许我们该强硬一点
Maybe we should play some hardball.
不  要么帮忙  要么滚蛋
No. Either help out or get out.
如果你们要出声...
If you open your mouth...
希望你们会提供建设性的办法
I expect you to offer up a solution.
我不会再说第二遍
I'm not gonna say it again.
-喂  -知道我是谁吗
-Hello? -Do you know who this is?
知道
Yeah.
你被关在哪了
Where are you being held?
我不在监狱
I'm not in prison.
那你在哪
Where are you?
我不能说
I can't say.
我需要你在洛杉矶帮我取点东西
I need you to get something to me in L.A.
阿历克斯
Alex.
不是什么危险的东西  求你了  我...
It's nothing dangerous. Please, I-I...
我不知道我还有多少时间
I don't know how much more time I have here.
听着  别让我做什么...
Look, don't ask me to do something...
你只需要去一趟杜兰哥的住宅中介就行了
You just need to reach out to the residential agency in Durango.
阿历克斯  不行
Alex, no.
你知道他们做了什么吗
Do you know what they did?
他们杀了我的儿子
They killed my son.
They killed my boy.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
只要说你愿意帮我
Just say that you'll help me.
求你了
Please?
我需要你的帮助
I just need your help.
我要找到凶手
I need to find out who did it.
求你了
Please.
听着  我知道在福克斯河的时候你要对我保密
So listen, I know in Fox River you had to keep secrets from me.
现在不需要了
You don't now.
怎么了
What's going on?
赛尔夫说我们今天一定要找到下一个持卡者
Self said we have until the end of the day to find the next cardholder.
否则我们全部要回监狱
Or we all go back to prison.
我知道你保释了斯科菲尔德和布伦斯
I know that you bailed out Scofield and Burrows.
而且我知道他们不在德克萨斯的监狱里
And I know they aren't in a supermax in Texas.
但你知道他们在哪  对吧  布鲁斯
But you know where they are, don't you, Bruce?
你别再找麻烦了
You don't want any more trouble than you're already in.
我不是有麻烦的那个人
I'm not the one in trouble.
让我帮你放松一下
Let me help you relax.
真是美好的一天
It's a beautiful day.
阳光明媚
The sun is shining.
你能感觉到微风拂过吗
Do you feel that gentle breeze?
今天真是个...
It's a great day...
家庭野餐的好日子
For a family picnic.
你不这么认为吗  布鲁斯
Don't you think so, Bruce?
六张卡
Six cards?
当初你可不是这样告诉我的  当
That's not what you sold me, Don.
我知道这超出了我们的预想
I realised it's more than we anticipated.
是超出你的预想
More than you anticipated! .
已经有人问我...
I already have people questioning me...
关于我们编造的重型监狱的事了
About the supermax line we're selling.
整件事就是一个错误
This whole thing was a mistake.
不  这件事没错
No,no, this wasn't a mistake.
斯科菲尔德在24小时内就帮我们得到一张...
Scofield got us a card within 24 hours...
要被送到洛杉矶的卡
Of being dropped in Los Angeles.
他知道自己在做什么
He knows what he's doing.
听着  我愿意冒险  做好我的工作
Look, I'm willing to take the risk and do my job.
我不明白为什么你不能
I don't understand why you aren't.
国土安全部还没确定名称  你还没长毛的时候
I've been in Homeland Security since before it even had a name!
我就在这工作
Since before you even had a single short and curly...
那你就该清楚现在的利害关系  主任
Then you should know what's at stake here, Director.
如果你不下令停止  我们就可以阻止
We could stop it, but not, not if you end this now.
我现在就给达洛参议员挂电话
I'm calling Senator Dallo now.
看看他是否想此事就此结束
I will see if he want shis thing killed or not.
但他是听我的建议的  当
But he follows my recommendations, Don.
先生  已将你到达伦敦的时间...
"Sir, changed your late London arrival...
改为7月16日下午4点
Now 7/16 at 4:00 p.m."
今天是16号
Today's the 16th.
他的日程里没有伦敦  对吧
There's nothing about London in his calendar, is there?
我们看是没有  没有
Not that we've seen, no.
没有任何来回英国的计划
Nothing about travel to or from the UK at all?
没有  什么都没有
No, nothing.
既然他在伦敦没有会面日程...
Now, why would he get an e-mail about an arrival in London...
为何他会收到关于抵达伦敦的邮件呢
When he has no business scheduled there?
可能这封邮件是一个...
It's probably because the e-mail is a...
暗号
Code.
阿历克斯  我很高兴你加入我们
Alex, I'm so glad you joined us.
S-C-Y-L-L-A  锡拉
S-C-Y-L-L-A, Scylla
今天4点的会议室是关于锡拉的
The meeting today at 4:00 is about Scylla.
我们可以假设塔克豪恩不是安排...
I think we can assume that Tuxhorn did not schedule...
自己同自己会面  所以...
A meeting with himself, so that...
会面的地点就是找到下一个持卡者的地方
Is where we're going to find our next cardholder.
好  那么下午4点是时间  还缺地点
Okay, so 4:00 p.m. is our when, we need a where.
如果你需要一个秘密的会面
If you were having a secret meeting.
不会把所有的信息一次都发送
You wouldn't send all the information together.
为了保险  时间和地点的信息会分开发送
You'd send the where and the when separately as a precaution.
还有其他和伦敦的邮件...
Were there any other e-mails sent to Tuxhorn...
同时发给塔克豪恩的吗
At the same time as the London e-mail?
伦敦的邮件发出几秒钟后
Within a few seconds of the London mail.
同一IP地址又发送了两封邮件
Two more e-mails followed from the same IP path.
就在这时  硬盘没有空间了
But that's when my device ran out of hard drive space.
追踪到了IP地址  但没有记录下内容
It picked up the IP address, but not the content.
追踪IP地址  找到发信人
Trace the IP address and find out who sent these e-mails.
听着  邮件会经过世界上很多服务器转移
Oh, look, e-mails get bounced to routers all over the world.
在到达收件箱之前
Before they end in your inbox.
无论邮件寄送到哪里  都会留下缓存文件
Wherever the mail's been, it leaves a shadow file.
根据地理位置  我判断这些邮件...
Based on the geography, I'm guessing these e-mails...
在塔克豪恩收到之前  可能在阿纳海姆的...
Probably squatted at the Anaheim server cluster...
服务器上停留过十亿分之一秒
A nanosecond before reaching Tuxhorn.
所以那就缓存文件的所在
So that's where you're going to find your shadow file.
那就去找
So get it.
拿着8位机的家伙不一定都能黑进航空航天局
Not every geek with a Commodore 64 can hack into NASA.
我是说  这些服务器...
I mean, these servers...
这些服务器有更多的防火墙
Have more firewalls than the devil's bedroom.
你们想要这些邮件  对不起
You want those e-mails, I'm sorry.
他们是在阿纳海姆的主服务器上
It's on a main server in Anaheim.
有可能在那个服务器上找到那些邮件吗
Is this possible to find those e-mails at that server?
从技术上说  是的
Technologically possible, yeah.
那我们去阿纳海姆
Then we're going to Anaheim.
你们两个去塔克豪恩工作的地方
I want you two to go to Tuxhorn's workplace.
找到他  如果看见他  跟住  告诉我们
Stake it out, if you see him, tail him, call us.
你以为你能大摇大摆靠近服务器吗
You think you're just going to walk up to a main server?
你知道那里会有保安的  对吧
You know there's going to be security, right?
我们别无选择  找到那封邮件...
We don't have a choice, we have to find that e-mail message...
我们就能找到会面地点
We can find out where the meeting is.
找到会面地点  就能找到下一个持卡者
Find out where the meeting is, we find our next cardholder.
-明白吗  -我们才能不蹲监狱
-Got it? -We stay out of jail.
是的  祝你好运  伙计
Yeah, well, good luck, man.
实际上  你要和我们一起去
Actually, you're coming with us.
再说一次  赛尔夫让我坐在这里...
Guess again. Self told me to sit here...
负责电脑方面的事情
And make with the clickety-clack on the keyboard.
我哪也不去
I'm not going nowhere.
是吗  跟着来吧
Oh yeah, you are.
有人吗
Hello?
欢迎回到...
"Instahomes welcomes you home...
家具齐全的公寓
To your furnished apartment."
你为什么一定要找这个人
Why must you go after this man?
在我的家乡  有个词叫宿敌
Where I come from, there's something called a blood feud.
你会回来的  对吗
You're coming back, right?
迈克尔・斯科菲尔德太多次对我见死不救
Michael Scofield left me for dead one too many times.
好消息  布鲁斯
Good news, Bruce.
你最喜欢的阿姨去野餐了
Your favorite aunt made it to the picnic.
她带来了柠檬水
She brought lemonade.
侄子侄女们在...
The little couns are...
在池塘里游泳
swimming in the pond.
兄弟姐妹们在...
Brothers and sisters are...
在碧绿的草原上...
Playing catch in a lush...
追逐打闹
Green field.
所有人都来了
Everyone is here.
基本算是所有人
Well, almost everyone.
两个很重要的人没来
Two very important people are missing.
迈克尔・斯科菲尔德和林肯・布伦斯在哪
Where are Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows?
我不知道
I don't know.
没关系的  布鲁斯
That's okay, Bruce.
我肯定你很快就会想起来了
I'm sure you'll remember soon.
享受野餐吧
Just enjoy the picnic.
你好  我是斯蒂芙妮・雷德
Hi, uh, my name is Stephanie Reed.
我是来人力资源部面试的
I'm here for a job interview with human resources.
好的
Okay, then.
不好意思  系统里没有你的名字
Sorry, your name's not in the system.
你能再看下吗  是R-E-E-D
Um, would you look again under R-E-E-D?
当然
Sure.
知道吗  她应该松开上衣的几个扣子
You know, she should drop a few buttons on that shirt.
警卫就会把邮件给她
The guard will give her the e-mails.
好极了
Great.
说
Yes.
你在阿纳海姆吗  Michael
You're in Anaheim, Michael?
现在可不是去迪斯尼好时候
This is a strange time to be taking a trip to Disney.
听我说  我向你保证  如果你要逃跑...
Listen to me, I promise you, if you're trying to run...
我在帮你找另外一张卡
I'm trying to get you another card.
从哪  明日世界吗
From where? Tomorrowland?
从主服务器上的一封邮件里
From an e-mail on a main router.
我们认为今天下午4点有一个锡拉的会面
We think there's a Scylla meeting this afternoon at 4:00.
-在哪  -希望在邮件中能找到答案
-Where? -Hopefully that information will be on the e-mail.
迈克尔  我们没有时间了
Michael, we're running out of time.
那就别再浪费我的时间
Then stop wasting mine.
我挂电话了  我挂电话了
I got to go, I got to go.
你和达洛参议院谈过了
Did you talk to senator Dallo?
是的  谈过了  现在我要和你谈谈
Yes, I did, and now I need to talk to you.
我要取消这个行动
I'm shutting it down.
对不起  小姐  我没找到任何你的预约
Sorry, ma'am, I don't have you down for any meeting today.
好吧  但临时工工会说过...
Okay, um... the, uh, the temp agency said...
他们要举行一次面试
That they were going to set the interview.
再次抱歉
Again, I'm sorry.
好吧
Okay.
今天找个保姆是很难得
It was really hard to get a sitter today.
你能否给人力资源部打个电话...
Would you be willing just to call human resources and see...
看看他们愿不愿意见我一面吗
If they'll see me since I'm here?
好的
Sure.
你好  我是前台的提姆
Hey, it's Tim at the front desk.
我这有一个叫斯蒂芙妮・雷德的...
Yeah, I've got a Stephanie Reed...
她说她是来面试的
She said she had a job interview.
斯蒂芙妮・雷德  R-E-E-D
Stephanie Reed, R-E-E-D.
她刚刚把保安卡交给迈克尔了
She just passed it off to Michael.
服务器机房可能在任何房间
Server room could be anywhere in here.
网络和配线技术条件都要求...
Network and wiring specifications require...
服务器只能在一楼
A server that's on the first floor,
中心位置  就像那里
Centrally located, like right there.
你是干嘛的  工程师还是什么
What are you, an engineer or something?
你确定你知道怎么做吗
Are you sure you know how to drive this thing?
是的  但要花点时间  我可不想被抓住
Yeah, but it's going to take a while and I don't want to get busted.
放松点  找到那些邮件
Just relax and find those e-mails.
听着  在我偷窃的时候  我在家里做...
Listen, man, when I steal, I do it from my home, in my boxers...
吃着大包的薯片  明白吗
Eating a bowl of Krispity Krunch, okay?
不会被看到  也不会被抓住
No chance of being seen, no chance of getting caught.
快点搞吧
Just get it done.
好的
Okay.
没事
All right.
快点  迈克尔  快点
Come on, Michael, come on.
女士
Hey, lady.
得到我要的东西了吗
Did you get what I need?
是的  得到了
Yeah, I got it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我知道你在计划什么  阿历克斯
I know what you're planning, Alex.
但听我说
But listen to me.
如果你抓到他了  打电话给我
If you do track him down, call me.
别做对你自己不利的事
Don't do something that could get you hurt.
我不会的
I won't.
你要的东西会在5点到
So the material will be where you asked by 5:00 p.m.
阿历克斯  我非常遗憾
And Alex, I'm so sorry.
再见  兰
Good-bye, Lang.
抱歉  他们今天无法见你
I'm sorry, they can't see you today.
我也无能为力了
And there's nothing more I can do.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你帮忙  我很感激
Thank you for your help, I appreciate it.
是哪个临时工工会让你来的
What was the name of the temp agency that sent you?
或许我们可以...
Uh, maybe we can...
给他们打电话解决这件事
Call them tother and figure this all out.
我记在车里了
I have it written down in my car.
我的保安卡在哪  宝贝
Where the hell's my security badge, sweetheart?
从桌子上消失了
It ain't at my station.
你刚来的时候还在那的
It was there when you showed up.
把你的手拿开  我没拿你的保安卡
Take your hands off me, I don't have your badge.
好  让我们检查一下
Yeah, well, we'll see about that.
莎拉有麻烦了
Sara's in trouble.
怎么了
What's going on?
她被发现了
She's been made.
迈克尔  莎拉被发现了
Michael, Sara's been made.
她没事吧
Is she all right?
保安发现她了  你们得马上离开
The guard has her, you got to get out of there now.
罗兰  我等会回来
Roland, I'll be back.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
继续干活
Just keep working.
我说过了  我没拿你的保安卡
Like I said, sir, I don't have your badge.
抱歉  我要走了
Excuse me, I need to leave.
你可以把你的故事讲给警察听  小姐
You can tell your story to the cops, sister.
别动
Don't move.
搞什么
What the hell?
罗兰  怎么样了
Roland, talk to me.
马上就好  马上就好
We're almost there, almost there.
我们得走了
We got to go.
我们现在必须离开了
We got to go now.
好了
Got it!
门怎么打不开了
Why won't the door open?
那他妈的是什么
What the hell is that?
是安全防护装置
It's a fail-safe device.
一旦当报警器响起  便会启动
Activated when the alarm gets pulled.
保护服务器不会被火灾破坏
To protect the server from fire damage.
你他妈的按了什么
What the hell did you pull it?
这是一幢老楼
This is an old building.
-不该有这么先进的装置的  -是吗
-It shouldn't have such an advanced system. -Oh, yeah?
很显然有  怎么办
Well, clearly it does. Wha-Wha-What's it do?
为了灭火  这个房间所有的氧气都会被抽光
To kill the fire, it sucks all the oxygen out of this room.
迈克尔  你到底在哪
Michael, where the hell are you?
这里的人越来越多了
It's getting crowded out here.
林肯  我们被困住了
Linc, Linc, we're trapped.
-我们在服务器室  -什么
-We're in the server room. -What?
这里是密封的
It's sealed.
氧气正在被抽出
They're sucking all the oxygen out.
我们还有2或3分钟的氧气剩余
We've got two, maybe three minutes of air left.
林肯
Linc?
我无法呼吸了
I can't breathe.
冷静点  冷静点
Calm down, calm down.
你越慌越糟糕
You panic, it gets worse.
快
Come on.
我们走
Let's go.
你觉得我们呆在车里有用吗
You think it's better on wheels?
不  我们别无选择
No, we ain't got no choice.
我们必须等  看他是否会出现
We got to wait and see if he shows up.
我不是在说找塔克豪恩的事
I'm not talking about finding Tuxhorn.
我是在说找那些卡
I'm talking about finding the cards.
我是在说要找到6张卡的事
I'm talking about finding six cards,
我是说我们是否有...
And I'm talking about whether we have...
哪怕那么一点的成功的机会
A snowball's chance in Haiti of actually doing this deed.
总比没机会好
Better than no chance.
我们离墨西哥只有几小时车程
Just saying we're a couple hours from Mexico.
我不介意有个能说当地语言的人...
And I wouldn't mind having someone with me...
和我一起去
Who could actually speak the native tongue.
做你该做的事  布拉德
Just do your job, Brad.
感觉好吗  布鲁斯
You feeling good, Bruce?
你看上去不错
You look great.
你的父亲  乔什
Your father, Josh.
很高兴你能参加家庭野餐聚会
Is so happy you made it to the family reunion picnic.
他非常想念你
He's missed you very much.
我的父亲已经死了
My father is dead.
没错
That's right.
他死了
He is.
你看  布鲁斯
You see that, Bruce?
你刚刚如实回答了我的问题
You just told me the truth in response to something I said.
因为现在撒谎是非常困难的
Because lying is so hard right now.
但说出事实却轻而易举
But telling the truth is so easy.
告诉我真相
So tell me the truth
告诉我参加野餐的人都想知道的事
Tell me what everyone at the picnic wants to know.
告诉我迈克尔・斯科菲尔德和林肯・布伦斯在哪
Where are Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows?
我  我不  我不知道
I, I don-- I don't know.
布鲁斯
Bruce.
一场大风暴就要来了
A bad storm's coming.
非常猛烈的风暴
A real bad storm.
当・赛尔夫
Don Self.
很好
Good.
议员的确收到我的留言了
So, so the senator did get my message?
不  不  抱歉  明天就太迟了
No, no, I'm sorry, tomorrow's too late.
我现在就要和他讲话
Okay, I-I-I need to speak to him now.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
赛尔夫特工  该走了
Agent Self, it's time to go.
保罗爷爷比萨点
Pappa Paul's Pizza Palace.
我要一个大号的...
Yeah, I'd like a large...
多加香肠和奶酪的披萨
With extra pepperoni and extra cheese.
诺比特
The Knobbit.
欲女列车
Add Momma To The Train.
业余试镜  第九集
Amateur Screen Tests #9.
胜者出现了
And we have a winner.
感谢致电伽特公司  有什么可以帮您
Thank you for calling GATE. How may I help you?
第一封邮件是克雷斯迪亚药品的广告
The first e-mail is an ad for Discretia.
壮阳药邮件
An e-mail for pecker pills?
你要电话吗
You want the number?
好极了
That's great.
绝对值得我用命去换
Definitely worth almost losing my life for.
第二封邮件是张邀请...
Second e-mail's an invitation...
加入一个天文观察家的俱乐部的请帖
To join some kind of stargazers' club.
星相能用于定位地球上某个位置
You know, constellations can be used to track points on Earth.
有个网站可以给出...
There is a website launches into the coordinates...
星座图  根据时间日期...
Of star patterns, and depending on the date...
它能找出地球相应的地点
It'll pick a corresponding location on the earth.
你知道这个是因为...
And you know this because...?
因为我儿子和...
Because my son and...
我前妻  我以前会上这个网站
my ex and... and I used to go on this site
这样他们抬头看天  就知道我在哪了
So they could look up at the sky and know where I was.
不是这个  那个星座对应的是南极洲
That's not it, that constellation's over Antarctica.
他不可能从洛杉矶出发  在今天下午...
He's not going to get there today by 4:00 p.m....
4点之前到那
Not from L.A.
那么  我差一点死的毫无价值
So, I almost died for nothing.
-很高兴知道这点  -很多人都死了
-That's good to know. -A lot of people have died.
那是他们的问题  好吗
Well, that's their problem, okay,
因为用命去换这个垃圾的人
Because anyone who gives up their life for this crap.
是傻蛋
Is a sucker.
因为你们根本赢不了
'cause you guys can't win!
再说那些死了的人
Say it about the people who died.
说啊
Say it.
阿历克斯
Alex.
起来
Get up.
回你那呆电脑那  干你的事去
Get back on your nerd box and do your job.
我们可以在湖边找个地方
We can get a little place by the water.
这比你独自亡命天涯好多了
And you'd be better off not being on the run by yourself, either.
我替你保证过的  贝里克
I vouched for you, Bellick.
我跟迈克尔说过  布拉德帮我逃到芝加哥
I told Michael, "Brad I helped me get to Chicago.
他是个好人  相信他
He's a good guy, trust him."
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
现在当我们都有机会...
And now you just want to run...
洗脱罪名的时候  你只想着逃跑
When we have a chance to clear our names?
但这个情形可不乐观
Odds of that don't look so good.
油箱是满的  油门在右边
Tank's full, gas pedal's on the right.
我们可以逃离这里
I say we get the hell out of Dodge
现在  等我们过边境之后再担心...
right now, we can worry about the ankle bracelets...
脚踝跟踪器也不迟
Once we get over the border.
你给我听着
You listen to me.
我现在只关心一件事
There's only one thing I'm thinking about.
她重7磅  眼睛和她妈妈长得一样
She weighs seven pounds, has her mother's eyes.
她的小手心牵挂着我的心
And my heart in the palm of her tiny hands.
所以无论让我找1张卡
Oo if I have to find one card.
或是6张卡
Or six cards.
或是6百万张卡
Or six million cards.
我都会不顾一切的去找
I'm going to do whatever it takes.
因为我只抱过我的小乖女儿10秒钟...
'cause I only got to hold my baby girl for ten seconds...
那远远不够
And that wasn't nearly long enough.
你想干什么
What are you doing?
这家伙不会出现了
This guy ain't showing up.
把手举到我们能看到的地方
Hey, get your hands where we can see them!
举起手来  举起手来
Get your hands up! Get your hands up!
-老天  情况不妙  -举起手来
-Oh, my God, this ain't good. -Put your hands up.
我举起来了  我举起来了
I got them up, I got them up!
把手举起来  苏克雷  快点  老兄
Put your hands up, Sucre, come on, man.
-你打给谁?  -等等
-Who you calling? -Hold on.
他们会崩了你的
They're gonna shot you.
快点  把手举起来
Come on, put your hands up!
好了  好了  别开枪  别开枪
Okay, okay, don't shoot, don't shoot.
别开枪  伙计  我们什么都不会做的
Don't shoot, man, we're all right.
电脑挂了
Computer's frozen.
-什么叫挂了  -我不知道
-What do you mean, it's frozen? -I-I don't know.
就是没反应了
It's just not responding.
我都重启两次了  还是不好用
I've rebooted twice now. It's still not letting me on.
再试一下
Try again.
我试了中止路由  强行指令
Look, I've tried a stop route, a jock program.
甚至后门登陆  我是说  你蹲过监狱
Even a back-door entry, I mean, you were in prison.
我肯定你对这个很熟悉
I'm sure you're familiar with that one.
你想死吗
You want to stop breathing?
怎么了
What happened?
他们把我锁死了
They locked me out.
我告诉你  他们要放弃我们了
I'm telling you, they're shutting us down.
我们得走了  他们来了
We gotta go. They're coming after us. Whoa.
我们快走  快点  等等
We gotta go, let's go, come on. Whoa, whoa.
等等  如果我们逃跑  他们会干掉我们的
Wait a minute, we run, they shoot us!
那你留下
Stay.
-莎拉  -什么
-Sara? -Yeah.
我们快离开这里
Let's get out of here.
你说过我们有一天的时间的
You said we'd have until the end of today.
不  这件事已经不受我控制了
No, this goes way over my head.
听着  这个计划已经被终止了
Look, this project's been terminated.
现在停车  结束这一切
Now pull over and end this.
我们能完成任务
We can finish the job.
已经没有任务了  知道吗
There is no more job, okay?
如果这件事曝光  回监狱...
If you make this takedown public, going back to prison.
将是你们最好的结果了
Is going to be the least of your worries.
甩掉他
Lose him.
跟住他  跟住
Stay on him, stay on him.
我们上  我们上
Let's go, let's go!
这边  快
It's this way, go!
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
这里是伽特公司  需要什么帮忙吗
Thank you for calling GATE. How may I help you?
是的  你好  我叫科尔・普发
Yes, hi, my name is Cole Pfeiffer.
我想问问关于始发奖金的事
Uh, I'm calling about my, uh, commencement bonus.
我到现在还没有收到
I haven't received it yet, and, uh...
当然  普发先生
Oh, of course, Mr. Pfeiffer.
不过怀特先生现在不在
Um, Mr. White is out right now,
他肯定是非常不想错过您的电话的
But he's going to be so upset he missed your call.
我试试找一下他
Here, let me try to track him down.
不  不  不用麻烦了
Oh, no, no, don't bother.
你寄张支票给我就行了
Uh, maybe you just could, uh, uh, forward the check to me.
不行  支票都需要怀特先生亲自签发的
No, Mr. White has to sign off on any checks.
而且我知道他非常想和你谈谈
And I know that he really wants to talk to you.
我让他给您回电话
So can I have him reach you...
您看可以吗
At the number that came up on my I.D.?
非常期待
Looking forward to it.
你他妈的为什么要告诉赛尔夫...
Why the hell did you tell Self...
我们今天能找到一个持卡者
That we could get a cardholder by today?
是他这么要求的  阿历克斯
He set the terms, Alex!
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice!
现在我们都没有选择了
And now none of us have a choice.
我绝对不会回监狱
And I am not going back to prison.
我还需要去...
And I still have this that I need...
-绝不回去  -那你跑啊
-Not going back. -Go ahead and run!
伙计们  别吵了
Guys, stop.
脚腕上绑着这东西...
We ain't running anywhere...
我们跑哪都没有用  知道吗
With these things on our ankles, all right?
在那里
It's over here.
这边
It's this way.
等等
Wait a minute.
Wait a second.
信号  信号没了
The signal...the signal's gone.
信号没了
The signal is gone.
他们跑哪去了
Where are they?
我们得找到信号  去找信号
Okay, we gotta go and get the signal, let's get the signal.
我们不能永远呆在这里
We cannot stay here forever.
他们肯定会找到的
They will eventually figure this out.
我不在乎这里能否阻止信号
I don't care if this place blocks the signal or not.
迈克尔  你在干嘛  伙计
Mike, what the hell are you doing, man?
我们没时间了
We don't have time for this.
答案就在这里  肯定在这里
The answers are in here, they have to be.
如果我能找到的话  也许我们还有机会
If I can just find them, we might have a chance.
这是广告  这些都是废话
It's an ad, the words don't make sense.
-都是胡扯  -没错  只有这样...
-It's gibberish. -Exactly, and that's what...
他们才能隐藏信息
Makes them ideal for hiding data.
别管那他妈的什么持卡者了
Forget about the damn cardholder.
赛尔夫已经不需要我们了
Self pulled the plug on us.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
是的  没事
Yeah, yeah.
我们会想出办法的
We're going to figure this out.
我们很擅长在绝境中脱身
We're getting good at pulling off the impossible.
妈的  我不是死而复生了吗  对吧
Hell, I came back from the dead, right?
这是什么
What is it?
你看到什么了
What do you see?
是放在一起看的
They go over each other.
发电厂
Power plant.
新港海滩
New beach.
新港海滩那有座发电厂
There's a power plant in Newport Beach.
那就是会面的地点
That's your meeting.
现在到下午4点时间不多了
We ain't got long until 4:00.
我们怎么才能从这逃出去
How the hell are we going to get out of here?
你能跑多快
How fast can you run?
有信号了吗
Have you got the signal?
是的  他们向西面跑了  四个街区
Yeah, they are heading west, four blocks.
走
Go!
让开  妈的
Move, damn it.
-干嘛  -下车
-What? -Get out of the cab.
你想干嘛
What hell do you think you're doing?
你好
Hello?
科尔・普发  我是格里高里・怀特
Cole Pfeiffer, Gregory White here.
抱歉打扰你了  先生  我打电话是想...
Oh, sorry to disturb you, sir, I was just calling.
询问一下奖金的事情
Bbout the, the bonus stipend.
打扰  你在说什么啊  孩子
Bother me? What are you talking about, son?
我非常高兴终于能...
I'm just thrilled to finally be able...
听见你的声音了  更好的是...
To put a voice to the e-mail, and better yet...
我终于能和你见面交谈了
I'm going to be able to put a face to the voice.
是的  因为我们还没见过面
Right, because we haven't met yet.
是的  这简直是罪过  我的朋友
Yes, and that is a crime, my friend.
我得告诉你  伽特公司这里有很多人...
I gotta tell you, there are a lot of people over here...
都非常期待能够和你见面
At GATE who are very excited about meeting you.
但我和我老婆明天就要去圣弗朗西斯科了
but I'm going off to San Francisco tomorrow with my wife.
我希望在走之前能同你见面
I'd love to see you before I go.
你明天一早就来伽特公司如何
So why don't you come to GATE first thing in the morning?
我想我们可以从...
I think we can all learn something...
东北区的销售冠军那里学到一些东西
From the number one salesman in the entire Northeast Region.
这就是伽特公司教会我们的东西
Weit...it's what GATE teaches.
通过你的知识...
"You can unshackle others...
来帮被束缚的人解脱
With the keys of knowledge."
这就是我要分享的东西
It...I...it's what I'm here to share,
这就是我知道的  也是我想分享的
It's what I know, it's what I want to give back.
瞧  这就是我开这家公司的目的
See, that's why I started this company.
让人们可以摆脱消极的束缚
So that people can avoid "The Captivity of Negativity."
向您致敬  怀特先生
Amen to that, Mr. White.
我得走了  我还要赶顿午餐
Now I gotta go, I've got a lunch.
不过明天一早我们在伽特公司见
But I'll see you at GATE first thing tomorrow,
我会准备好你的办公室  加你到工资系统中
And I'll set your office up, get you in the payroll system
而且我会亲手把奖金给你
And I will personally hand you your bonus check.
明天我们在伽特公司见
Well, I'll see you at GATE tomorrow, then.
拿好球棒  科尔・普发
Grab a bat, Cole Pfeiffer.
教练让你上场了
Coach just put you in the game.
真是个奇怪的见面地点
Strange place for a meeting.
有些神神秘秘  你不这样觉得吗
A little cloak-and-dagger, don't you think?
一如既往  塔克豪恩  一如既往
Belts and suspenders, Stuart, belts and suspenders.
为什么是老挝
Why Laos?
医生第一次不会去解剖人的尸体
A doctor doesn't perform his first dissection on a human cadaver.
首先从青蛙开始  然后是猪
First, he learns on a frog, then a pig,
然后某天  就是人了
Then one day, a human.
老挝是我们的青蛙
Laos is our frog.
也许丹麦或者乍得会是我们的猪
Perhaps Denmark or Chad will be our pig.
然后  只要我们想  所有东西都是的尸体
After that, anything we want can be our cadaver.
好  我们去检查一下电站的另一面
All right, let's check on the other side of the complex.
他们可能在那里会面
They could be meeting there.
跑
Run!
别动  布伦斯
Don't move, Burrows.
不许动
Don't you move an inch.
我抓住你了
I'm taking you down.
别动
Don't move.
站住  别跑
Hold! Stop!
快跑
Go.
-你确定吗  -是的  快走
-Are you sure about this. -Yeah, go.
站住  别动
Freeze. Don't move.
举起手来  放在我能看到的地方
Hands up. Keep your hands where I can see 'em.
过来
Aah! Come on.
别跑  站住
Stop! Hold it!
把手举起来
Hands up.
别动
Hold it.
把手放在我能看到的地方
Let's see your hands.
把他拷起来
Get him up.
斯科菲尔德跑了
Scofield ran.
不用多久就能抓到他的
Won't take long to find him.
你只是在做无用的拖延
You're just delaying the inevitable.
-不可避免事是锡拉的会面  -闭嘴
-What's inevitable is a meeting with Scylla. -Shut up!
把他押进车子
Put him in the car.
听着  我们看了塔克豪恩的掌上电脑
Listen. We went through Tuxhorn's pda.
他们在这幢楼的另一边碰头
They got a meeting on the other side of that building.
-结束了  -没有结束
-It's over. -It's not over.
结束了  林肯  好吗
It's over, Lincoln, okay?
我知道你希望成功
I know you wanted this to work out.
但现在我已经不能控制了
But it's beyond me now.
好吧  结束了
Okay, it's Done.
我得听从命令  结束了
I have orders. It's over.
还没结束
It's-it's not.
结束了
It's finished!
那么将军  行动到底什么时候开始
So, when exactly does the op-order commence, general?
已经开始了
It already has.
不  我是说  什么时候能得到结果
No. I mean, when do we see ramifications?
我告诉你  塔克豪恩
I'll tell you what, Stuart.
你应该关心的是千兆赫器和海底钻探
You worry about the gigahertz and the offshore drilling.
我来负责行动的事
Let me worry about the op-orders.
他们到了
There they come.
怎么处置她
What about her?
让她走
Let her go.
真正的胜利者们
Hey, hey, real group of winners.
你把我卷进来  当
You hooked me up with here, Donnie.
非常感谢  我很感激
Thanks a lot. I appreciate it.
听着  伙计  我们都是带徽章的人
Look, man, we both have worn the badge in our day.
我不能再被关起来了
I-i can't survive any more time in lock-up.
我们能不能想点办法
Can-can we please work something out?
不  你可以快点滚进车去  进去
No. You can work your ass into this van. Get in.
恭喜  公司赢了
Congratulations. Company wins.
快  进去
Come on, get in.
-什么  -进去
-What? -Get in.
一定是在玩笑
You got to be kidding me.
是迈克尔
It's Michael.
别紧张
Easy.
我给过你一个很好的开始
I gave you a good enough head start.
你应该好好利用
Should have took advantage of it.
是啊  但那样我就无法给你这个了
Yeah, but then I wouldn't have been able to give you this.
看录像吧
Press the video function.
这不两个锡拉...
It wasn't a meeting...
持卡者的会面  赛尔夫特工
Between two Scylla cardholders, agent Self.
这是6个持卡者的会面
It was a meeting between all six cardholders.
现在我们知道谁拥有其他5张卡了
So now we know who has the other five cards.
这该有所意义吧
And that should mean something.
即使对一个毫无话语权的人也是吧
Even to someone whose word means nothing.
我现在要给达洛参议员挂电话
I'm gonna call senator Dallo now.
但他听我的建议  当
But he follows my recommendations, Don.
下次你再逃跑的话
The next Time you run from me.
我不会再开车追你
I'm not gonna be chasing you down in a car.
我会一枪打死你
It's gonna be with a bullet in your back.
让他们走  所有人
Let them go, all of them.
让他们走
Let them go.
带他们去仓库
Put them in the warehouse.
所有的人
All of them.
是的  我是当・赛尔夫
Yeah, it's Don Self.
我现在就要和他讲话
I need to talk to him right now.
现在
Right now.
很快会有那么一天  我们会把你的小船开走
Some day soon, we're gonna drop that lifeboat of yours.
永远不再回来
In the water and disappear forever.
我保证
I promise.
那个孤僻先生要去哪
Hey, where's Mr. Personality going?
他们检查他的脚踝了吗  因为他一定...
They check his wrists? 'Cause he must...
别管他的事
Let him be.
不服从上级的命令  是吧
Insubordination's tiring, huh?
你何时学会直接给达洛参议员打电话了
Where the hell do you get off calling Senator Dallo directly?
你不能到我的地盘
You don't move into my city.
到我的办公室  就把我踩在脚下
Into my regional office and go over my head!
你要我怎么做
What do you want from me?
你知道游戏规则的  赫博
You know how it works, Herb.
你以为公司要杀你的时候
You think when the Company's breathing down your neck.
达洛参议员会出面救你吗
Senator Dallo's gonna bring in the cavalry?
他会假装从来不认识你
He'll pretend he's never even heard of you.
现在你只能靠自己了  赛尔夫
You're on your own from now on, Self.
你要孤军奋战了
You're an island.
如果我孤军奋战  你还在这干吗
If I'm an island, what are you doing here?
出去  让我把我的活干完
Get out of my office and let me finish what I started.
我会出席你的葬礼...
When you do get buried...
给你挖第一铲子土的
I'll be the first one there with a shovel.
很好  到时见
Great. See you then.
莎拉・唐克雷蒂 ...
Sara Tancredi's...
在某个安全的地方对吗  布鲁斯
Somewhere safe, isn't she, Bruce?
你会保证她的安全的  对吗
You would have made sure of that, wouldn't you?
告诉我  莎拉在哪
So tell me, where is Sara?
你不会不知道莎拉藏的那个...
Why wouldn't you find a way to Sara...
安全的地方在哪的
Where it's safe.
安全
Safe.
洛杉矶吗
Los Angeles?
洛杉矶的哪里
Where in Los Angeles?
我不知道
I don't know.
我相信你
I believe you.
做的好
Good job.
野餐结束了  布鲁斯
Picnic's over, Bruce.
马宏怎么了
What's up with Mahone?
他们杀了他儿子
They murdered his son.
公司杀了他儿子...
The Company killed his son like...
就像他们曾经想要杀LJ那样
Like they tried to kill LJ.
阿历克斯  我...
Alex, I, uh...
我知道发生了什么事
Uh, I-I know what happened.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
他们这么做
They did this...
是要找到我
To get to me.
逼我出来
To flush me out.
他们让我的前妻...
And then they let my ex-wife...
活着...
stay alive...
为了让她亲口告诉我  如果我不出现...
Just so she could tell me that she was next...
他们就杀了她
If I didn't turn myself in.
现在他们把她藏起来
Now she's in protective custody,
而我在这个破仓库里...
And I'm living in a warehouse trying to find...
想要找出是哪个混蛋杀了我儿子
Those of a bitch who killed my kid.
我们在这里都是有原因的
We're all here for something.
每个人都是有原因的
All of us are here for something.
你必须坚持到最后一刻
You need to stay focused until this is done.
我能做到
I can do my job.
我保证
I promise.
很好
Good.
我保证我会不惜一切代价...
And I promise I'll do whatever it takes...
帮你找到杀你儿子的凶手
To help you find the person that killed your son
和幕后主使
And the people behind the hit.
我们会找到这些家伙的  阿历克斯
We're gonna get these guys, Alex.
我会帮你的
I'm gonna help you.